If you dare to mess with the Liu family,
you, as my legal counsel,
will be fired today.
As long as I am the CEO of Lin Group,
she, as my legal counsel,
will not be fired.
In the eyes of some people,
you, me,
and your brother
are just pawns.
You are used when needed,
and can be abandoned
or sacrificed
when not needed
or threatening.
Enough.
I don't want to hear your big talk.
I just want to know
if you sent
this anonymous email.
Did you know
Wen Shiyi had this trick up her sleeve?
Did you stir up trouble between me and Lin Jiming
just to wait until today,
until I had nowhere to turn and came to you?
Ms. Liu,
you're very smart.
But your imagination
could be even more creative.
If I sent it,
why would I be anonymous?
I could have just taken these things
and negotiated with you.
Wouldn't that be better?
What's the point
of me being anonymous,
other than to alert you,
making you rush into my office
like you did today?
Then how do you explain all this?
How do you
seem to know everything?
Because I saw through Wen's true nature
long before you did.
And because
I won't let myself
end up like you
or your brother,
just another pawn she discards.
To protect yourself,
you must know your opponent inside out,
including her tactics.
Using others' weaknesses
and past grievances to eliminate rivals.
This is her classic move.
Targeting your brother,
it was expected.
Self-preservation.
Your goal is just to protect yourself?
I don't believe you.
Everything you do
is aggressive.
The best way to protect yourself
is to make the people who threaten you disappear.
Isn't that right?
Ms. Liu,
we now have a common enemy.
Wen Poetic not only wants to destroy your family's peace,
but also is hindering me.
More importantly,
she thinks we are both
soft targets that can be easily manipulated.
And then?
After using me to take down Wen Poetic,
is the next target
my family?
Do you
have something
on me?
To be honest,
I do.
About your brother,
and the South City land,
I know as much as Wen Shiyi.
But
I'm not like her.
I want to remove obstacles
and stand firmly,
not to make endless enemies.
A fallen Wen Shiyi
is the most valuable to me,
not a Lin Group with countless enemies
with countless enemies.
Keeping your Liu family safe
is only beneficial for me
to take over the Lin family's project
in the future.
This is a simple test of interests.
Fine.
Guan Tiantian,
I'll trust you this time,
not because of your character,
but
your intelligence
and judgment of interests.
I hope
you're right.
I won't let you down.
Now I need you to use your auditing power
to investigate the abnormal capital flow
of the UK subsidiary three years ago.
I think
that's her weakness.
Guan Tiantian,
sometimes,
I really admire you.
If we met under different circumstances,
we might have become good friends.
It's not too late now.
Pleasure working with you.
The alliance
was officially formed at this moment
based on fear,
interests,
was officially formed.
Xiaoyu,
you're here.
Mom,
this is Lawyer Guan,
my friend.
Lawyer Guan,
you look
just like Xiaoyu.
I heard you're not feeling well,
so I came to see you.
Auntie,
are you feeling any better?
It's just an old problem.
Well,
get some rest.
If there's anything you want to eat,
just let me know, and I'll get it for you.
Ah,
that's alright.
Your work is more important.
Go ahead.
Thank you for visiting my mom.
She's been in a daze lately.
But as soon as she's awake,
she keeps talking about Yu.
She will get better.
How about you?
How are you doing lately?
You seem to have something on your mind.
It's nothing serious.
Anyway,
safety comes first.
After all,
you are my friend.
OK.
By the way,
I have stopped
handling the case of Bai Qiang.
The person we sent to the UK reported back that
the death certificate of Gu Qingyu is indeed true.
But there's no record of her cremation
in the hospital.
Guan Yu knows I like sculptures.
That's really thoughtful.
Know yourself and your opponent,
and you'll always be victorious.
The sense of fragmentation and alienation
is portrayed so realistically.
She shows an unusual avoidance
towards her family,
the past,
and accidents,
and even
physiological disgust.
You're not here to climb the social ladder,
but to collect debts.
Zhan Shan,
is it really Gu Qingyu?
She's back.
What you need is all here.
I made a backup of the original
and hid it away.
By the way,
Wen Shiyi
urged me to issue the final report yesterday.
Hold her off.
We need time
to make the evidence work.
Then
what about my brother?
As long as Wen Shiyi falls,
the things in the anonymous email
will have no source.
When necessary,
we can use it
to counter Wen's frame-up.
Yes.
Mr. Wen.
I knew it.
Tell me.
She looked into the flow of funds
from the UK subsidiary,
and also
Zhou Qi's whereabouts after he left.
But
there's no record in the system.
She's not here to check the accounts,
but to dig up the past.
But Zhou Qi
immigrated to South America three years ago.
She shouldn't find anything.
What if she does?
She must disappear.
Zhan Shan,
you go handle it personally.
Zhan Shan
Whether Jiming can hold his position
depends on
how ruthless we are.
Yes.